<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>
  <plugin id="in.kkkev.jj-idea" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/download/v0.7.8/jj-idea-0.7.8.zip" version="0.7.8">
    <idea-version since-build="251.0" />
    <name>Jujutsu VCS Integration</name>
    <description><![CDATA[
      <p>Native IntelliJ integration for <a href="https://jj-vcs.github.io/jj/">Jujutsu (jj)</a>, a Git-compatible version control system with a fundamentally different approach to working with code.</p>

      <h3>Why Jujutsu?</h3>
      <p>Jujutsu treats your working copy as a commit—always. No staging area, no "dirty" state. Just describe what you're working on and keep coding.</p>

      <h3>Key Features</h3>
      <ul>
          <li><b>Describe-First Workflow</b> — Working Copy tool window for describing current work and creating new changes.</li>
          <li><b>Custom Log View</b> — Visual commit graph with inline change IDs, descriptions, and bookmarks.</li>
          <li><b>Change Operations</b> — Edit, abandon, and describe changes directly from the log.</li>
          <li><b>File History &amp; Annotations</b> — Full file history with diff viewer and line-by-line blame.</li>
          <li><b>Multi-Repository Support</b> — Work with multiple JJ repositories in a single project.</li>
          <li><b>Real-Time Status</b> — Auto-refresh keeps the UI in sync as you edit files.</li>
      </ul>

      <p><a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">GitHub</a> · <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues">Issues</a></p>
    ]]></description>
    <vendor email="jj-idea@kkkev.in" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">Kevin Thomas</vendor>
    <change-notes><![CDATA[
      <h3>0.7.8</h3>
      
<h4>Fixed</h4>
<li>Ignore scan no longer walks into ignored directories (e.g. `node_modules`, `build`) on every working-copy refresh. Ignored directories are now pruned at entry and reported as a single entry, fixing the multi-second stall and 10s shutdown hang reported in GitHub #35.</li>
<li>Read-access error (`RuntimeExceptionWithAttachments`) no longer logged when showing a diff from the History view or using Compare with Local, Compare Before with Local, Open File, or Compare File with Branch actions.</li>
<li>Working-copy switcher widget no longer paints doubled (two icons and two copies of the text).</li>
<li>Filter components (reference, author, date) now show the correct X close icon immediately after IDE restart when a filter is active — previously the icon stayed as a dropdown arrow until the filter was interacted with.</li>
<li>Status bar widget no longer throws an EDT-access exception on startup in projects with Jujutsu repositories.</li>
<li>Working-copy panel no longer flickers or lags with 40+ changed files. Rapid file-save bursts (e.g. save-all over a large working copy) are coalesced into a single tree rebuild per 200ms window using `MergingUpdateQueue`, and bulk VFS events now issue a single batched `filesDirty()` call instead of one call per file.</li>

<h4>Changed</h4>
<li>Improved log performance when expanding context around a commit in large repositories.</li>

<h4>Added</h4>
<li>Multiple independent log windows: click the **+** button in the VCS tool window tab strip to open a new tab (all repos, default name). In projects with both Git and Jujutsu, the action appears in Git's existing "▼" dropdown. Right-click any Jujutsu log tab → **Rename…** to rename it inline. All filter state (search text, reference, author, date, root filter selection) and layout (column visibility, widths, details position) persists per-window across restarts.</li>
<li>Tag create/set and delete actions (requires jj 0.37+): right-click a commit in the log to set a tag at that revision, or expand the "Tag" submenu to delete an existing tag. Right-clicking a tag chip directly also offers a delete action. Moving an existing tag prompts for confirmation. The bookmark and tag chip plumbing (URI scheme, hit-testing, popup dispatch) is now unified.</li>
<li>Show repository roots in change trees and bookmark widget menus using coloured repository icons.</li>
      <p>See <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/tag/v0.7.8">full release notes</a> for details.</p>
    ]]></change-notes>
  </plugin>
</plugins>
