<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>
  <plugin id="in.kkkev.jj-idea" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/download/v0.7.10/jj-idea-0.7.10.zip" version="0.7.10">
    <idea-version since-build="251.0" />
    <name>Jujutsu VCS Integration</name>
    <description><![CDATA[
      <p>Native IntelliJ integration for <a href="https://jj-vcs.github.io/jj/">Jujutsu (jj)</a>, a Git-compatible version control system with a fundamentally different approach to working with code.</p>

      <h3>Why Jujutsu?</h3>
      <p>Jujutsu treats your working copy as a commit—always. No staging area, no "dirty" state. Just describe what you're working on and keep coding.</p>

      <h3>Key Features</h3>
      <ul>
          <li><b>Describe-First Workflow</b> — Working Copy tool window for describing current work and creating new changes.</li>
          <li><b>Custom Log View</b> — Visual commit graph with inline change IDs, descriptions, and bookmarks.</li>
          <li><b>Change Operations</b> — Edit, abandon, and describe changes directly from the log.</li>
          <li><b>File History &amp; Annotations</b> — Full file history with diff viewer and line-by-line blame.</li>
          <li><b>Multi-Repository Support</b> — Work with multiple JJ repositories in a single project.</li>
          <li><b>Real-Time Status</b> — Auto-refresh keeps the UI in sync as you edit files.</li>
      </ul>

      <p><a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">GitHub</a> · <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues">Issues</a></p>
    ]]></description>
    <vendor email="jj-idea@kkkev.in" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">Kevin Thomas</vendor>
    <change-notes><![CDATA[
      <h3>0.7.10</h3>
      
<h4>Added</h4>
<li>The "Compare with Another Commit…" popup and the working-copy switcher now accept arbitrary revision expressions (change id, git SHA, bookmark name) that fall outside the loaded log window. Typing a query that matches nothing locally shows a "Use … as revision" fallback, which resolves in the background and upgrades to a full commit preview, including the correct mutability icon.</li>

<h4>Changed</h4>
<li>Ignored-file scanning now runs asynchronously off the modified-file refresh path. Working-copy changes appear immediately after a save regardless of ignored-tree size; the Commit toolwindow shows the built-in "updating" indicator while ignored files are computed in the background.</li>
<li>In multi-repository log windows, the repository color gutter is now expanded by default (showing the repo name) instead of collapsed to a thin colored strip, making per-repo colors easier to discover. Each log tab remembers your collapse/expand choice (GitHub #10).</li>

<h4>Fixed</h4>
<li>Bookmark and tag chips in the commit details panel no longer break apart when wrapping to multiple lines — the icon could previously be separated from its label, and long hyphenated names could break mid-word; each chip now wraps as a single atomic unit.</li>
<li>Typing a revision that doesn't exist in the revision-choice popup or working-copy switcher no longer logs a WARN-level entry; resolution failures for a single typed revision are now logged at INFO, since this is an expected outcome rather than a plugin error.</li>
<li>Mutable/immutable icon in the working-copy switcher and revision-choice popup now correctly reflects the target commit's immutability for bookmarks and tags, even when the target is outside the loaded log window.</li>
<li>Resolving conflicts now refreshes the working copy so resolved files no longer appear conflicted in the panel; re-opening the Resolve dialog after a successful resolution no longer throws "Could not extract conflict data".</li>
      <p>See <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/tag/v0.7.10">full release notes</a> for details.</p>
    ]]></change-notes>
  </plugin>
</plugins>
