<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>
  <plugin id="in.kkkev.jj-idea" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/download/v0.7.5/jj-idea-0.7.5.zip" version="0.7.5">
    <idea-version since-build="251.0" />
    <name>Jujutsu VCS Integration</name>
    <description><![CDATA[
      <p>Native IntelliJ integration for <a href="https://jj-vcs.github.io/jj/">Jujutsu (jj)</a>, a Git-compatible version control system with a fundamentally different approach to working with code.</p>

      <h3>Why Jujutsu?</h3>
      <p>Jujutsu treats your working copy as a commit—always. No staging area, no "dirty" state. Just describe what you're working on and keep coding.</p>

      <h3>Key Features</h3>
      <ul>
          <li><b>Describe-First Workflow</b> — Working Copy tool window for describing current work and creating new changes.</li>
          <li><b>Custom Log View</b> — Visual commit graph with inline change IDs, descriptions, and bookmarks.</li>
          <li><b>Change Operations</b> — Edit, abandon, and describe changes directly from the log.</li>
          <li><b>File History &amp; Annotations</b> — Full file history with diff viewer and line-by-line blame.</li>
          <li><b>Multi-Repository Support</b> — Work with multiple JJ repositories in a single project.</li>
          <li><b>Real-Time Status</b> — Auto-refresh keeps the UI in sync as you edit files.</li>
      </ul>

      <p><a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">GitHub</a> · <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues">Issues</a></p>
    ]]></description>
    <vendor email="jj-idea@kkkev.in" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">Kevin Thomas</vendor>
    <change-notes><![CDATA[
      <h3>0.7.5</h3>
      
<h4>Added</h4>
<li>Navigating to a commit that is outside the configured log limit (e.g. clicking a parent change ID in the details panel or an annotation line) now expands the log to show a context window around the target commit and selects it. In multi-repository projects, each repo's expansion accumulates additively — expanding a commit in repo A then repo B shows both context windows together. Clicking the Refresh toolbar button returns the log to the configured limit view.</li>

<h4>Fixed</h4>
<li>Working copy changes no longer require a manual refresh to appear on startup. Two fixes: (1) the change provider skips `jj status` until the working copy state is loaded (eliminating a wasted invocation), and (2) the working copy panel now reads from the `ChangeListManager` cache when it connects to `workingCopies`, so changes are visible immediately even if the panel was created after the initial VCS scan completed.</li>
<li>Fixed a memory leak reported on IDE shutdown: `JujutsuCommitDetailsPanel` was registered in the Disposer tree under `ROOT_DISPOSABLE` instead of its owning panel, causing a `RuntimeException` on quit.</li>
<li>Diff views for mutable revisions no longer show stale content after the revision is edited: cached file bytes are invalidated on `logRefresh` and re-fetched lazily on next access.</li>

<h4>Changed</h4>
<li>Git remote lookup is now backed by `NotifiableState` (consistent with working copy and repository state) instead of a per-repository `CompletableFuture`. Remotes are refreshed whenever the repository set changes, and BGT callers are guaranteed a loaded result via `immediateValue` rather than silently receiving an empty list during startup.</li>
<li>Rebase, squash, move-bookmark, and revision-picker dialogs now open without issuing extra `jj log` calls when the main log is already loaded — they reuse the cached commit data instead.</li>
<li>Single-revision lookups via `getLogEntry` now route through the in-memory `LogCache` for `ChangeId`, `CommitId`, and `BookmarkName` targets, falling back to a targeted `jj log -r` shell-out only on a cache miss or unknown revision type. Removed the dead `repositoryStates` state (superseded by `workingCopies`) and eliminated the redundant `jj log` fetch fired when the working-copy panel binds to a repository (the cached working copy entry from `workingCopies` is already applied by the `boundRepository` setter).</li>
<li>The status-bar working-copy switcher resolves bookmark and commit-ID selections from the cache on a cache hit, avoiding an extra `jj log` call per switch.</li>
      <p>See <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/tag/v0.7.5">full release notes</a> for details.</p>
    ]]></change-notes>
  </plugin>
</plugins>
