<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>
  <plugin id="in.kkkev.jj-idea" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/download/v0.7.15/jj-idea-0.7.15.zip" version="0.7.15">
    <idea-version since-build="251.0" />
    <name>Jujutsu VCS Integration</name>
    <description><![CDATA[
      <p>Native IntelliJ integration for <a href="https://jj-vcs.github.io/jj/">Jujutsu (jj)</a>, a Git-compatible version control system with a fundamentally different approach to working with code.</p>

      <h3>Why Jujutsu?</h3>
      <p>Jujutsu treats your working copy as a commit—always. No staging area, no "dirty" state. Just describe what you're working on and keep coding.</p>

      <h3>Key Features</h3>
      <ul>
          <li><b>Describe-First Workflow</b> — Working Copy tool window for describing current work and creating new changes.</li>
          <li><b>Custom Log View</b> — Visual commit graph with inline change IDs, descriptions, and bookmarks.</li>
          <li><b>Change Operations</b> — Edit, abandon, and describe changes directly from the log.</li>
          <li><b>File History &amp; Annotations</b> — Full file history with diff viewer and line-by-line blame.</li>
          <li><b>Multi-Repository Support</b> — Work with multiple JJ repositories in a single project.</li>
          <li><b>Real-Time Status</b> — Auto-refresh keeps the UI in sync as you edit files.</li>
      </ul>

      <p><a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">GitHub</a> · <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues">Issues</a></p>
    ]]></description>
    <vendor email="jj-idea@kkkev.in" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">Kevin Thomas</vendor>
    <change-notes><![CDATA[
      <h3>0.7.15</h3>
      
<h4>Added</h4>
<li>"Compare with Working Copy" in the log's right-click menu diffs every file that differs between the selected commit and your working copy, in one editor tab with the working-copy side editable — handy for reviewing everything since a target commit and editing it directly for a final `jj absorb`. ([#40](https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues/40))</li>
<li>The References/Bookmarks selector above the log now also lists bookmarks that exist only on a remote and aren't tracked locally, shown as `name@remote` with a distinct icon, so you can start work off a remote branch without tracking it first. ([#47](https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues/47))</li>
<li>New "Tracked" checkbox in the right-click menu for selected files (Project view, editor, Working Copy panel, Commit view) that match a `.gitignore` rule lets you force-include or stop tracking them, without touching `.gitignore` by hand. The checkbox updates instantly, and a notification confirms what happened (or explains why it didn't). ([#42](https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues/42))</li>
<li>The commit details panel now shows the author's (and committer's, when different) email address alongside their name, as a clickable mail link, with the date/time kept together on one line when it wraps. ([#51](https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues/51))</li>
<li>New "New Change" quick action creates a change without prompting for a description upfront (the common case, since you'll usually squash it in later). It's the primary option in the log's right-click menu (the old dialog-based flow is kept as "New Change with Description..."), and is bound to Cmd/Ctrl+Shift+N while the log is focused. ([#51](https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues/51))</li>
<li>New and Edit buttons in the log toolbar act on the selected change with one click, without opening the right-click menu. ([#51](https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues/51))</li>
<li>New "Fit Columns to Window Width" option (Columns menu) shrinks the description and other columns as the log window narrows so horizontal scrolling is rarely needed, e.g. on a laptop screen or with the details pane docked beside the log. On by default for tabs you haven't customized; tabs where you've already resized a column keep your exact layout and scrolling as before. ([#51](https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues/51))</li>

<h4>Fixed</h4>
<li>Selecting a commit in the log no longer resets the table's horizontal scroll position. ([#51](https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues/51))</li>
<li>On a narrow log window, the filters no longer crowd out the New/Edit/Refresh/Fetch/Push/Columns buttons. Filters that don't fit collapse into a "»" menu instead, with any filter you've actually applied kept visible longer than ones you haven't. ([#51](https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues/51))</li>
<li>The New button in the log toolbar now greys out instead of disappearing when there's no selection, matching how the Edit button already behaved.</li>
      <p>See <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/tag/v0.7.15">full release notes</a> for details.</p>
    ]]></change-notes>
  </plugin>
</plugins>
