<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>
  <plugin id="in.kkkev.jj-idea" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/download/v0.7.11/jj-idea-0.7.11.zip" version="0.7.11">
    <idea-version since-build="251.0" />
    <name>Jujutsu VCS Integration</name>
    <description><![CDATA[
      <p>Native IntelliJ integration for <a href="https://jj-vcs.github.io/jj/">Jujutsu (jj)</a>, a Git-compatible version control system with a fundamentally different approach to working with code.</p>

      <h3>Why Jujutsu?</h3>
      <p>Jujutsu treats your working copy as a commit—always. No staging area, no "dirty" state. Just describe what you're working on and keep coding.</p>

      <h3>Key Features</h3>
      <ul>
          <li><b>Describe-First Workflow</b> — Working Copy tool window for describing current work and creating new changes.</li>
          <li><b>Custom Log View</b> — Visual commit graph with inline change IDs, descriptions, and bookmarks.</li>
          <li><b>Change Operations</b> — Edit, abandon, and describe changes directly from the log.</li>
          <li><b>File History &amp; Annotations</b> — Full file history with diff viewer and line-by-line blame.</li>
          <li><b>Multi-Repository Support</b> — Work with multiple JJ repositories in a single project.</li>
          <li><b>Real-Time Status</b> — Auto-refresh keeps the UI in sync as you edit files.</li>
      </ul>

      <p><a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">GitHub</a> · <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues">Issues</a></p>
    ]]></description>
    <vendor email="jj-idea@kkkev.in" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">Kevin Thomas</vendor>
    <change-notes><![CDATA[
      <h3>0.7.11</h3>
      
<h4>Fixed</h4>
<li>A file newly created inside an ignored directory (e.g. matching a `.gitignore` pattern) now appears under "Ignored Files" in the Changes view immediately, without requiring a second edit to `.gitignore` to trigger a refresh.</li>
<li>Opening a newly created ignored or unversioned file no longer produces a spurious warning in the IDE log.</li>
<li>The ignored-file scan's slow-scan watchdog now reliably fires on directories containing very many files (previously it only checked elapsed time once per directory entered, so a single huge flat directory could block past the 5s threshold without ever showing the "scan is slow" notification). The watchdog now also aborts the in-progress scan when it fires, instead of letting it run to completion (GitHub #35).</li>
<li>The log and working-copy view no longer fail to load entirely on jj backends that can't evaluate the `remote_bookmarks()` revset (e.g. some non-standard jj implementations). The plugin now falls back to loading the log without the "pushed to remote" decoration on affected repositories instead of crashing (GitHub #35).</li>
<li>A commit with many bookmarks no longer hides the description or silently clips part of the bookmark list in the log table. Bookmarks/tags are now capped to half the column's width, with any overflow collapsed behind a clickable "+N more" chip that opens a popup of the hidden refs.</li>
<li>The log row hover tooltip no longer gets clipped by the screen for commits with many bookmarks. It now reflows the bookmark list across multiple lines and scrolls if the content is taller than the screen, instead of cutting off the description and/or bookmarks.</li>
      <p>See <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/tag/v0.7.11">full release notes</a> for details.</p>
    ]]></change-notes>
  </plugin>
</plugins>
