<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>
  <plugin id="in.kkkev.jj-idea" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/download/v0.7.12/jj-idea-0.7.12.zip" version="0.7.12">
    <idea-version since-build="251.0" />
    <name>Jujutsu VCS Integration</name>
    <description><![CDATA[
      <p>Native IntelliJ integration for <a href="https://jj-vcs.github.io/jj/">Jujutsu (jj)</a>, a Git-compatible version control system with a fundamentally different approach to working with code.</p>

      <h3>Why Jujutsu?</h3>
      <p>Jujutsu treats your working copy as a commit—always. No staging area, no "dirty" state. Just describe what you're working on and keep coding.</p>

      <h3>Key Features</h3>
      <ul>
          <li><b>Describe-First Workflow</b> — Working Copy tool window for describing current work and creating new changes.</li>
          <li><b>Custom Log View</b> — Visual commit graph with inline change IDs, descriptions, and bookmarks.</li>
          <li><b>Change Operations</b> — Edit, abandon, and describe changes directly from the log.</li>
          <li><b>File History &amp; Annotations</b> — Full file history with diff viewer and line-by-line blame.</li>
          <li><b>Multi-Repository Support</b> — Work with multiple JJ repositories in a single project.</li>
          <li><b>Real-Time Status</b> — Auto-refresh keeps the UI in sync as you edit files.</li>
      </ul>

      <p><a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">GitHub</a> · <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues">Issues</a></p>
    ]]></description>
    <vendor email="jj-idea@kkkev.in" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">Kevin Thomas</vendor>
    <change-notes><![CDATA[
      <h3>0.7.12</h3>
      
<h4>Added</h4>
<li>Splitting allows selection of specific hunks within files.</li>
<li>You can now support me to keep working on this plugin! See the *Sponsor this plugin** link at the bottom of **Settings → Version Control → Jujutsu**.</li>

<h4>Fixed</h4>
<li>Opening a file with F4 from the commit details or working-copy changes panel no longer logs a "Synchronous execution on EDT" error. The same fix covers Show Diff, Show Diff in New Tab, and Compare File with Branch when invoked from a changes selection.</li>
<li>Filtering the commit log (by text, author, date, reference, or root) no longer leaves the graph lines misaligned or pointing at hidden commits. The graph layout is now recomputed from the visible subset whenever the filter changes, and the renderer is updated before Swing repaints so no intermediate misaligned state is shown.</li>
<li>Resolving a conflict now updates the Working Copy panel automatically — previously the file kept showing as conflicted even after clicking Refresh, and trying to resolve it again would throw an error.</li>
      <p>See <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/tag/v0.7.12">full release notes</a> for details.</p>
    ]]></change-notes>
  </plugin>
</plugins>
