<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>
  <plugin id="in.kkkev.jj-idea" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/download/v0.7.2/jj-idea-0.7.2.zip" version="0.7.2">
    <idea-version since-build="251.0" />
    <name>Jujutsu VCS Integration</name>
    <description><![CDATA[
      <p>Native IntelliJ integration for <a href="https://jj-vcs.github.io/jj/">Jujutsu (jj)</a>, a Git-compatible version control system with a fundamentally different approach to working with code.</p>

      <h3>Why Jujutsu?</h3>
      <p>Jujutsu treats your working copy as a commit—always. No staging area, no "dirty" state. Just describe what you're working on and keep coding.</p>

      <h3>Key Features</h3>
      <ul>
          <li><b>Describe-First Workflow</b> — Working Copy tool window for describing current work and creating new changes.</li>
          <li><b>Custom Log View</b> — Visual commit graph with inline change IDs, descriptions, and bookmarks.</li>
          <li><b>Change Operations</b> — Edit, abandon, and describe changes directly from the log.</li>
          <li><b>File History &amp; Annotations</b> — Full file history with diff viewer and line-by-line blame.</li>
          <li><b>Multi-Repository Support</b> — Work with multiple JJ repositories in a single project.</li>
          <li><b>Real-Time Status</b> — Auto-refresh keeps the UI in sync as you edit files.</li>
      </ul>

      <p><a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">GitHub</a> · <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues">Issues</a></p>
    ]]></description>
    <vendor email="jj-idea@kkkev.in" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">Kevin Thomas</vendor>
    <change-notes><![CDATA[
      <h3>0.7.2</h3>
      
<h4>Added</h4>
<li>"Show Diff in New Tab" context menu action on file-change trees: opens a fresh diff editor tab each time, allowing multiple diffs to be open simultaneously alongside the reusable preview tab.</li>
<li>Diff preview editor tabs now show context in their title: working copy diffs show `@: filename`, log-detail diffs show `<short-change-id>: filename`, and multi-selection shows the count (e.g. `3 changes: filename`).</li>

<h4>Fixed</h4>
<li>Double-clicking a file in the working copy or log details file-change tree now opens a diff preview editor tab. Subsequent single-clicks on other files swap the diff content in the same tab rather than opening new tabs. Escape closes the preview. Cmd/Ctrl+D routes through the same preview tab when invoked from these panels.</li>
<li>Single-clicking a file in the working copy panel no longer opens a new editor tab on every click.</li>
      <p>See <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/tag/v0.7.2">full release notes</a> for details.</p>
    ]]></change-notes>
  </plugin>
</plugins>
