<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>
  <plugin id="in.kkkev.jj-idea" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/download/v0.6.7/jj-idea-0.6.7.zip" version="0.6.7">
    <idea-version since-build="251.0" />
    <name>Jujutsu VCS Integration</name>
    <description><![CDATA[
      <p>Native IntelliJ integration for <a href="https://jj-vcs.github.io/jj/">Jujutsu (jj)</a>, a Git-compatible version control system with a fundamentally different approach to working with code.</p>

      <h3>Why Jujutsu?</h3>
      <p>Jujutsu treats your working copy as a commit—always. No staging area, no "dirty" state. Just describe what you're working on and keep coding.</p>

      <h3>Key Features</h3>
      <ul>
          <li><b>Describe-First Workflow</b> — Working Copy tool window for describing current work and creating new changes.</li>
          <li><b>Custom Log View</b> — Visual commit graph with inline change IDs, descriptions, and bookmarks.</li>
          <li><b>Change Operations</b> — Edit, abandon, and describe changes directly from the log.</li>
          <li><b>File History &amp; Annotations</b> — Full file history with diff viewer and line-by-line blame.</li>
          <li><b>Multi-Repository Support</b> — Work with multiple JJ repositories in a single project.</li>
          <li><b>Real-Time Status</b> — Auto-refresh keeps the UI in sync as you edit files.</li>
      </ul>

      <p><a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">GitHub</a> · <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues">Issues</a></p>
    ]]></description>
    <vendor email="jj-idea@kkkev.in" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">Kevin Thomas</vendor>
    <change-notes><![CDATA[
      <h3>0.6.7</h3>
      
<h4>Added</h4>
<li>Jujutsu context menu available when viewing historical file versions</li>
<li>Show diff for historical change</li>
<li>Compare historical change with another commit</li>
<li>Custom history provider replaces built-in VCS history tabs</li>

<h4>Fixed</h4>
<li>Diffs, change lists, and annotation gutters now show the correct base content for merge commits, using the auto-merged parent tree instead of the first parent's content</li>
<li>Diffs work for files that have been renamed</li>
<li>Open in Remote finds last pushed revision</li>
<li>Restore Selection action no longer evaluates repository resolution unnecessarily when hidden in historical context</li>

<h4>Changed</h4>
<li>"Restore to This" now supports multiple file selections</li>
<li>Removed spurious opening of files from working copy window when selecting a file</li>
<li>Consolidated "Open File" and "Open Repository Version"</li>
<li>Split and squash actions consolidated for working copy and historical revisions</li>
<li>Open in Remote works for multiple files</li>
      <p>See <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/tag/v0.6.7">full release notes</a> for details.</p>
    ]]></change-notes>
  </plugin>
</plugins>
