<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>
  <plugin id="in.kkkev.jj-idea" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/download/v0.6.9/jj-idea-0.6.9.zip" version="0.6.9">
    <idea-version since-build="251.0" />
    <name>Jujutsu VCS Integration</name>
    <description><![CDATA[
      <p>Native IntelliJ integration for <a href="https://jj-vcs.github.io/jj/">Jujutsu (jj)</a>, a Git-compatible version control system with a fundamentally different approach to working with code.</p>

      <h3>Why Jujutsu?</h3>
      <p>Jujutsu treats your working copy as a commit—always. No staging area, no "dirty" state. Just describe what you're working on and keep coding.</p>

      <h3>Key Features</h3>
      <ul>
          <li><b>Describe-First Workflow</b> — Working Copy tool window for describing current work and creating new changes.</li>
          <li><b>Custom Log View</b> — Visual commit graph with inline change IDs, descriptions, and bookmarks.</li>
          <li><b>Change Operations</b> — Edit, abandon, and describe changes directly from the log.</li>
          <li><b>File History &amp; Annotations</b> — Full file history with diff viewer and line-by-line blame.</li>
          <li><b>Multi-Repository Support</b> — Work with multiple JJ repositories in a single project.</li>
          <li><b>Real-Time Status</b> — Auto-refresh keeps the UI in sync as you edit files.</li>
      </ul>

      <p><a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">GitHub</a> · <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues">Issues</a></p>
    ]]></description>
    <vendor email="jj-idea@kkkev.in" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">Kevin Thomas</vendor>
    <change-notes><![CDATA[
      <h3>0.6.9</h3>
      
<h4>Added</h4>
<li>Conflict resolution: conflicted files detected via `jj resolve --list` appear in red (MERGED_WITH_CONFLICTS) in the working copy panel</li>
<li>Three-way merge dialog opens on conflicted files showing ours / base / theirs; supports bulk Accept Yours / Accept Theirs</li>
<li>"Resolve Conflicts…" context menu action scoped to the selected files in the working copy panel, or the focused file in the editor; only visible when the selection contains conflicted files</li>
<li>Conflicted files now appear highlighted in the log details pane when a conflicted commit is selected</li>
<li>"Resolve Conflicts…" in the log row context menu for the working copy entry when conflicts are present</li>
<li>"Resolve Conflicts…" in the log details pane changes tree for working copy entries</li>

<h4>Fixed</h4>
<li>Conflict marker parsing handles all three jj formats — snapshot (`+++++++`), diff (`%%%%%%%`), and git (`|||||||`/`=======`) — including the git format introduced as the default in jj 0.37</li>
      <p>See <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/tag/v0.6.9">full release notes</a> for details.</p>
    ]]></change-notes>
  </plugin>
</plugins>
