<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>
  <plugin id="in.kkkev.jj-idea" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/download/v0.7.4/jj-idea-0.7.4.zip" version="0.7.4">
    <idea-version since-build="251.0" />
    <name>Jujutsu VCS Integration</name>
    <description><![CDATA[
      <p>Native IntelliJ integration for <a href="https://jj-vcs.github.io/jj/">Jujutsu (jj)</a>, a Git-compatible version control system with a fundamentally different approach to working with code.</p>

      <h3>Why Jujutsu?</h3>
      <p>Jujutsu treats your working copy as a commit—always. No staging area, no "dirty" state. Just describe what you're working on and keep coding.</p>

      <h3>Key Features</h3>
      <ul>
          <li><b>Describe-First Workflow</b> — Working Copy tool window for describing current work and creating new changes.</li>
          <li><b>Custom Log View</b> — Visual commit graph with inline change IDs, descriptions, and bookmarks.</li>
          <li><b>Change Operations</b> — Edit, abandon, and describe changes directly from the log.</li>
          <li><b>File History &amp; Annotations</b> — Full file history with diff viewer and line-by-line blame.</li>
          <li><b>Multi-Repository Support</b> — Work with multiple JJ repositories in a single project.</li>
          <li><b>Real-Time Status</b> — Auto-refresh keeps the UI in sync as you edit files.</li>
      </ul>

      <p><a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">GitHub</a> · <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues">Issues</a></p>
    ]]></description>
    <vendor email="jj-idea@kkkev.in" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">Kevin Thomas</vendor>
    <change-notes><![CDATA[
      <h3>0.7.4</h3>
      
<h4>Added</h4>
<li>Cmd+D / Ctrl+D on a selected log entry now opens the native diff preview — the same embedded tree+diff view you get by double-clicking a file in the commit details panel, with directory grouping and a `"abc1234: FileName.kt"` tab title. The action is also available in the log table's right-click context menu. "Open in New Tab" opens a standalone chain-viewer tab and likewise now works from a selected log entry.</li>

<h4>Fixed</h4>
<li>Toggling Description, Change ID, Status, or Decorations in the Columns menu now correctly shows or hides that content in the log view, rather than adding a duplicate column.</li>
<li>Copied files are no longer shown as merge conflicts in the working copy panel. They now appear as rename-style entries (source → destination) and are correctly shown in commit history.</li>
<li>Split, Rebase, Squash Into, and Squash From dialogs no longer silently fail when the relevant changes are not currently visible in the log (e.g. outside the display limit or filtered by the active revset). The Split preview graph now also appears when Split is opened from the Changes view.</li>
<li>Squash Into, Squash From, and Rebase destination/source pickers now populate immediately when the dialog opens.</li>
      <p>See <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/tag/v0.7.4">full release notes</a> for details.</p>
    ]]></change-notes>
  </plugin>
</plugins>
