<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>
  <plugin id="in.kkkev.jj-idea" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/download/v0.7.1/jj-idea-0.7.1.zip" version="0.7.1">
    <idea-version since-build="251.0" />
    <name>Jujutsu VCS Integration</name>
    <description><![CDATA[
      <p>Native IntelliJ integration for <a href="https://jj-vcs.github.io/jj/">Jujutsu (jj)</a>, a Git-compatible version control system with a fundamentally different approach to working with code.</p>

      <h3>Why Jujutsu?</h3>
      <p>Jujutsu treats your working copy as a commit—always. No staging area, no "dirty" state. Just describe what you're working on and keep coding.</p>

      <h3>Key Features</h3>
      <ul>
          <li><b>Describe-First Workflow</b> — Working Copy tool window for describing current work and creating new changes.</li>
          <li><b>Custom Log View</b> — Visual commit graph with inline change IDs, descriptions, and bookmarks.</li>
          <li><b>Change Operations</b> — Edit, abandon, and describe changes directly from the log.</li>
          <li><b>File History &amp; Annotations</b> — Full file history with diff viewer and line-by-line blame.</li>
          <li><b>Multi-Repository Support</b> — Work with multiple JJ repositories in a single project.</li>
          <li><b>Real-Time Status</b> — Auto-refresh keeps the UI in sync as you edit files.</li>
      </ul>

      <p><a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">GitHub</a> · <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues">Issues</a></p>
    ]]></description>
    <vendor email="jj-idea@kkkev.in" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">Kevin Thomas</vendor>
    <change-notes><![CDATA[
      <h3>0.7.1</h3>
      
<h4>Added</h4>
<li>"Squash Into Here from..." action in the log context menu: right-click on a destination change to pick one or more source changes to fold into it via `jj squash --from ... --into ...`. This is the inverse of "Squash from Here into..." — destination is pre-selected, sources are chosen. The working copy is pre-selected as a source when it is mutable. Supports multi-source selection, partial file selection, description combining, and the delete/move working-copy option.</li>

<h4>Changed</h4>
<li>Squash dialogs no longer automatically move the working copy to the destination after a squash. A new "Delete empty source change and move working copy to destination" checkbox gives explicit control over this behaviour; the last-used state is persisted per project and defaults to unchecked (matching vanilla `jj squash` semantics).</li>

<h4>Fixed</h4>
<li>"Squash Into…" destination picker now includes descendants of the source change. Previously descendants were incorrectly excluded (using rebase cycle-prevention logic that does not apply to squash).</li>
<li>Squash dialogs no longer send `--message` when jj would handle the description naturally. Descriptions are now only combined and sent when both the source and destination have non-empty descriptions and the squash is full (source will be abandoned). For partial squashes the destination description is left unchanged.</li>
<li>Log column widths are now correctly persisted across sessions. Previously, programmatic width assignments during panel initialization were triggering the save listener and overwriting user-adjusted widths with defaults before they could be restored.</li>
<li>"Squash into Parent…" is now enabled for merge commits. The dialog shows a destination picker restricted to the source's mutable parents; the user picks which parent to squash into. Previously the action was silently disabled for any commit with more than one parent.</li>
      <p>See <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/tag/v0.7.1">full release notes</a> for details.</p>
    ]]></change-notes>
  </plugin>
</plugins>
