<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>
  <plugin id="in.kkkev.jj-idea" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/download/v0.6.5/jj-idea-0.6.5.zip" version="0.6.5">
    <idea-version since-build="251.0" />
    <name>Jujutsu VCS Integration</name>
    <description><![CDATA[
      <p>Native IntelliJ integration for <a href="https://jj-vcs.github.io/jj/">Jujutsu (jj)</a>, a Git-compatible version control system with a fundamentally different approach to working with code.</p>

      <h3>Why Jujutsu?</h3>
      <p>Jujutsu treats your working copy as a commit—always. No staging area, no "dirty" state. Just describe what you're working on and keep coding.</p>

      <h3>Key Features</h3>
      <ul>
          <li><b>Describe-First Workflow</b> — Working Copy tool window for describing current work and creating new changes.</li>
          <li><b>Custom Log View</b> — Visual commit graph with inline change IDs, descriptions, and bookmarks.</li>
          <li><b>Change Operations</b> — Edit, abandon, and describe changes directly from the log.</li>
          <li><b>File History &amp; Annotations</b> — Full file history with diff viewer and line-by-line blame.</li>
          <li><b>Multi-Repository Support</b> — Work with multiple JJ repositories in a single project.</li>
          <li><b>Real-Time Status</b> — Auto-refresh keeps the UI in sync as you edit files.</li>
      </ul>

      <p><a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">GitHub</a> · <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues">Issues</a></p>
    ]]></description>
    <vendor email="jj-idea@kkkev.in" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">Kevin Thomas</vendor>
    <change-notes><![CDATA[
      <h3>0.6.5</h3>
      
<h4>Fixed</h4>
<li>Describe dialog no longer shows a literal `{0}` placeholder in the prompt; it now correctly shows the change ID being described</li>
<li>Deleting a remote bookmark no longer shows an error dialog with a missing resource string. Remote bookmarks (e.g. `main@origin`) no longer offer Delete or Rename actions; only Track/Untrack is offered for remote bookmarks</li>
<li>Diffs from merge working copies no longer fail. Previously, comparing against `@-` was ambiguous when the working copy had multiple parents, causing "cannot load diff" errors or showing files as entirely new. Now resolves to the first parent's change id from cached state</li>

<h4>Changed</h4>
<li>Marketplace description expanded to surface additional shipped features: compare with branch/revision, restore files, configurable revsets with Test button, per-repository setting overrides, push safety (non-fast-forward and sideways move warnings), multi-select in log, rebase post-rebase preview, split's dual-tree UI, Show History for Selection, and colocate option in clone/init</li>
<li>Roadmap trimmed: "Open in Remote" removed (shipped in 0.6.2/0.6.3); "Squash & Split from File Selection" narrowed to remaining destination-picker + hunk work; "Remote Bookmark Management" narrowed to branches panel and bookmark toolbar widget</li>
      <p>See <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/tag/v0.6.5">full release notes</a> for details.</p>
    ]]></change-notes>
  </plugin>
</plugins>
