<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>
  <plugin id="in.kkkev.jj-idea" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/download/v0.7.3/jj-idea-0.7.3.zip" version="0.7.3">
    <idea-version since-build="251.0" />
    <name>Jujutsu VCS Integration</name>
    <description><![CDATA[
      <p>Native IntelliJ integration for <a href="https://jj-vcs.github.io/jj/">Jujutsu (jj)</a>, a Git-compatible version control system with a fundamentally different approach to working with code.</p>

      <h3>Why Jujutsu?</h3>
      <p>Jujutsu treats your working copy as a commit—always. No staging area, no "dirty" state. Just describe what you're working on and keep coding.</p>

      <h3>Key Features</h3>
      <ul>
          <li><b>Describe-First Workflow</b> — Working Copy tool window for describing current work and creating new changes.</li>
          <li><b>Custom Log View</b> — Visual commit graph with inline change IDs, descriptions, and bookmarks.</li>
          <li><b>Change Operations</b> — Edit, abandon, and describe changes directly from the log.</li>
          <li><b>File History &amp; Annotations</b> — Full file history with diff viewer and line-by-line blame.</li>
          <li><b>Multi-Repository Support</b> — Work with multiple JJ repositories in a single project.</li>
          <li><b>Real-Time Status</b> — Auto-refresh keeps the UI in sync as you edit files.</li>
      </ul>

      <p><a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">GitHub</a> · <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues">Issues</a></p>
    ]]></description>
    <vendor email="jj-idea@kkkev.in" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">Kevin Thomas</vendor>
    <change-notes><![CDATA[
      <h3>0.7.3</h3>
      
<h4>Fixed</h4>
<li>Selecting an immutable change in the status-bar working-copy switcher no longer fails with "Commit … is immutable". The switcher now queries jj directly for the selected revision's immutability (no longer limited to the 10 most recent changes), acts on the commit id to avoid divergent-change ambiguity, and shows a confirmation dialog before switching. Immutable items are also dimmed with a lock icon in the popup.</li>

<h4>Changed</h4>
<li>Status-bar working-copy widget now renders a full styled row (commit icon + change ID + truncated description) via the shared `TextCanvas` renderer, replacing the plain-text display. The widget is no longer built on the internal `DvcsStatusWidget` API and now uses `CustomStatusBarWidget` for proper platform integration. Widget refresh is coalesced into a single handler and is freeze-safe; a `FileEditorManagerListener` updates the displayed repository when switching files in multi-root projects.</li>

<h4>Added</h4>
<li>A bookmark management widget now appears in the log toolbar. In single-repo projects it shows the current working-copy bookmark name(s) and opens a dropdown with per-bookmark sub-menus (Create, Rename, Delete, Forget; remote bookmarks folded in as Track/Untrack). In multi-repo projects the label is blank and the dropdown groups bookmarks under one sub-menu per repository, with "Create Bookmark Here…" scoped to each repo's working copy.</li>
<li>A working-copy switcher widget now appears in the bottom-right status bar for JJ-managed projects. It shows the current local bookmark name, falling back to the change description or `(no description set)`. Clicking opens a speed-searchable popup listing local bookmarks at the top, then up to 10 recent changes; bookmarks and changes are rendered with the same icons, colors, and styled IDs as the "Compare with Another Commit…" revision selector. Selecting an item shows a confirmation dialog to choose **Edit** or **New on Top** (`jj edit` / `jj new`); immutable targets offer only New on Top. The widget auto-refreshes reactively via the state model and hides for non-JJ projects.</li>
<li>Log table now correctly shows pending-deletion bookmarks: entries carrying a remote bookmark (e.g. `main@origin`) whose local counterpart has been deleted now display the deleted local (`main` with strikethrough) at that commit, and the remote no longer shows a spurious large ahead count.</li>
<li>Pending-deletion bookmarks (bookmarks deleted locally but still present on the remote) now appear in the "Specific bookmark" dropdown in the push dialog, shown with strikethrough and a "(deleted)" label. The confirmation dialog before a push now also warns when pending deletions will be included.</li>
<li>Bookmark decorations now show pending deletions (strikethrough), local/remote divergence (↑n ↓n), and bookmark conflicts (conflict icon) in the log gutter, graph column decorations, and commit details panel.</li>
<li>"Forget" context menu action on local bookmarks: removes a bookmark locally without creating a pending remote deletion. A confirmation dialog explains that the bookmark will reappear on the next fetch.</li>
<li>"Move Bookmark Here…" opens a searchable dialog that classifies bookmarks into Forward and Backward/Sideways sections with directional icons and full-width section dividers. Forward bookmarks can be selected immediately; backward or sideways moves are shown at 50% opacity and require checking "Allow backward or sideways move" to enable selection. If the repository state changes between opening the dialog and confirming, a fallback prompt handles the race condition.</li>
<li>Bookmark chips in the log table (Decorations column and inlined graph/description column) are now interactive: hovering shows a hand cursor, left-clicking navigates the log to the change that bookmark points at, and right-clicking opens a per-bookmark context menu with Rename, Delete, Forget, Track/Untrack, and Move To… actions.</li>
<li>Bookmark chips in the commit details panel are now interactive with the same left-click navigation and right-click context menu.</li>
<li>"Move \<bookmark\> To…" context menu action: opens a searchable change-picker dialog showing candidate destinations classified as Forward (descendants) or Backward (ancestors), with an "Allow backward move" checkbox to gate ancestor selection.</li>
      <p>See <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/tag/v0.7.3">full release notes</a> for details.</p>
    ]]></change-notes>
  </plugin>
</plugins>
