<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>
  <plugin id="in.kkkev.jj-idea" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/download/v0.7.16/jj-idea-0.7.16.zip" version="0.7.16">
    <idea-version since-build="251.0" />
    <name>Jujutsu VCS Integration</name>
    <description><![CDATA[
      <p>Native IntelliJ integration for <a href="https://jj-vcs.github.io/jj/">Jujutsu (jj)</a>, a Git-compatible version control system with a fundamentally different approach to working with code.</p>

      <h3>Why Jujutsu?</h3>
      <p>Jujutsu treats your working copy as a commit—always. No staging area, no "dirty" state. Just describe what you're working on and keep coding.</p>

      <h3>Key Features</h3>
      <ul>
          <li><b>Describe-First Workflow</b> — Working Copy tool window for describing current work and creating new changes.</li>
          <li><b>Custom Log View</b> — Visual commit graph with inline change IDs, descriptions, and bookmarks.</li>
          <li><b>Change Operations</b> — Edit, abandon, and describe changes directly from the log.</li>
          <li><b>File History &amp; Annotations</b> — Full file history with diff viewer and line-by-line blame.</li>
          <li><b>Multi-Repository Support</b> — Work with multiple JJ repositories in a single project.</li>
          <li><b>Real-Time Status</b> — Auto-refresh keeps the UI in sync as you edit files.</li>
      </ul>

      <p><a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">GitHub</a> · <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues">Issues</a></p>
    ]]></description>
    <vendor email="jj-idea@kkkev.in" url="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea">Kevin Thomas</vendor>
    <change-notes><![CDATA[
      <h3>0.7.16</h3>
      
<h4>Added</h4>
<li>The commit details panel now renders issue-tracker references (e.g. `JIRA-123`) and plain URLs in commit descriptions as clickable links, using your IDE's Version Control → Issue Navigation settings. Clicking one opens it in your browser. ([#15](https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues/15))</li>
<li>Double-clicking a commit in the log now shows its diff, and pressing Enter does the same — both are rebindable to a different action in Settings → Keymap. ([#51](https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues/51))</li>
<li>The log search field now matches a commit's Git hash (full or abbreviated), not just its change ID, description, or author. ([#44](https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues/44))</li>
<li>New "Duplicate Change" and "Duplicate Onto..." actions in the log's right-click menu create an identical copy of the selected change(s), either in place or onto a chosen destination — works on immutable changes too. The "Duplicate Onto..." dialog hides destinations and disables placements that would fail because they'd need to rewrite an immutable commit. ([#33](https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues/33))</li>

<h4>Fixed</h4>
<li>Pushing a new or untracked bookmark no longer fails on jj 0.42 and later with "unexpected argument '--allow-new'". You're now asked to confirm before the new bookmark is created on the remote, same as before. ([#53](https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues/53))</li>
<li>Pushing with the default "tracking bookmarks" scope no longer silently skips a brand-new bookmark with no feedback — you're now asked to confirm creating it on the remote, same as when pushing a specific bookmark.</li>
<li>Background operations (e.g. Git push/fetch) that hit an unexpected internal error now report it instead of appearing to do nothing.</li>
<li>The log graph now draws a merge commit's parents in the same left-to-right order as `jj log`, with matching line colors. Previously the parents could appear swapped (e.g. the trunk parent on the right) when a non-mainline parent happened to sit in the row directly below the merge. ([#51](https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues/51))</li>
<li>The commit log no longer shows a status icon on ordinary (mutable) revisions; only immutable revisions are marked, removing visual noise from the common case. ([#51](https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/issues/51))</li>
<li>Changing a log filter (reference/bookmark, author, date, text, or root) no longer deselects the current commit, or silently selects a different one, as long as it's still visible in the filtered list.</li>
<li>Commit pickers in dialogs (Rebase, Squash Into..., Duplicate Onto..., Move Bookmark) now always show commits in the same order as the main log, instead of sometimes showing an unrelated order (e.g. an immutable root commit before the changes on top of it). This could happen the first time a dialog was opened for a repo, and — in multi-repo projects — could affect any repo unpredictably, because different repos' root commits share the same underlying jj change ID and were getting conflated when merging repos' logs.</li>
      <p>See <a href="https://github.com/kkkev/jj-idea/releases/tag/v0.7.16">full release notes</a> for details.</p>
    ]]></change-notes>
  </plugin>
</plugins>
